DESMOND OFORI

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER





054-129-8861



oforidesmond@rocketmail.com



633 First Okle Road, Accra



ofori.vercel.app

SKILLS

- NodeJs /JavaScript
- ReactJS / React Native
- Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Express / MongoDB
- Redux
- PostgreSQL / GraphQL
- Project Management Tools
- Collab Tools (Git)
- Web Design
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication Skills
- Troubleshooting and Repair

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

ACCRA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2021 - 2024

CCNA CERTIFICATIONS

GHANA-INDIA KOFI ANNAN CENTRE **2014 - 2015**

CERTIFICATE IN HARDWARE

PROMAX COMPUTER TRAINING **2014**

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

NUNGUA SNR. HIGH SCHOOL 2011 - 2014

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional software-developer with four years of experience in web and mobile application design and currently employed as a Software Development Officer at infoGate.Net. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT OFFICER

INFOGATE.NET LIMITED

APRIL 2023 - PRESENT

- Crafting robust and scalable web and mobile applications using react, next JS, JavaScript, express JS, node, SQL, MongoDB, etc.
- Interact with external and internal API's.
- Manage the company servers and data.
- Providing technical support.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (INTERN)

WHITSUN SYSTEMS LIMITED

JUNE 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Web Application design
- Built the logic for a data logging application that scaled.
- Redesigned and upgraded web-applications for the company.

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

FREELANCE

2014 - PRESENT

- Assembled desktop computers for clients.
- Actively troubleshoot and repair PCs for clients
- Engaged in projects for the administering of computers to educational institutions.